ubreakifix.com 2019-08-28

# Privacy Policy | uBreakiFix

_This Privacy Policy was last modified on April 23, 2019._

UBREAKIFIX or the term “us”, “we”, or “our” refers to the owner of this website (www.ubreakifix.com). The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of this website. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information we receive from you online.

As part of the process of connecting to the website, the website automatically collects your internet protocol address/location, information your internet browser provides, and any information that is entered while visiting our website. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy We use your personally identifiable information only for providing and improving the website and providing service within our locations or over the phone. By using the website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

**Information Collection and Use**

While using our website or visiting any of our stores, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you regarding questions, comments, services requested, product offers, service updates, send confirmations, invoices, updates, and support and administrative messages. Personally identifiable information refers to information that is connected to your name and may include things such as your e-mail address, mailing address, or telephone number.

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's internet protocol address, browser type, browser version, and the pages of our webite that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

Search queries may be saved and data later used to see which pages on the website garner the most attention from customers.

The (location) data collected from your browser may be used to determine customer patterns of behavior in a given market. This knowledge allows us to improve our services in the future.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are small bits of information, which may include an anonymous unique identifier, that the UBREAKIFIX website places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on the website to make your visits to our website more enjoyable and valuable to you by providing a customized experience and recognizing your preferences when you visit our website. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website. UBREAKIFIX participates in behavior-based advertising. This means that a third party may use technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about your use of our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interest. That advertising may appear either on our website, or on other websites. 

**Sharing**

UBREAKIFIX may share your personally identifiable information with companies that are affiliated (that is, that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with UBREAKIFIX.

There may be instances when UBREAKIFIX may disclose personally identifiable information without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of UBREAKIFIX, other affiliated companies or their employees, agents, and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if UBREAKIFIX sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, UBREAKIFIX may transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party as part of that transaction.

**Security**

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use reasonable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

UBREAKIFIX may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to our Privacy Policy, we will change the modified date near the top of this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Access and Choice**

UBREAKIFIX has implemented the following procedure that you may use to access, correct, or delete your personally identifiable information, or choose how your information is used. If you would like to know the types of information that UBREAKIFIX collects from visitors to its website, please email or write us at the address listed below under “Contact Us”. If your personally identifiable information is incorrect, you may correct the information by sending a written request for correction to the address listed below. If you wish to stop receiving email marketing promotions from UBREAKIFIX, please click here the unsubscribe link included in the email.

**NAI Notice**

uBreakiFix may allow third-party companies, including ad networks, to serve advertisements, provide other advertising services and/or collect certain information when you visit our website.

Third-party companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

Third-party companies may use non-cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. These technologies may be used directly on this website. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising by those third parties that are members of self-regulatory programs such as the Network Advertising Initiative, please visit the NAI’s website (www.networkadvertising.org) which will allow you to opt out of Interest-Based Advertising by one, or all, NAI members.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at uBreakiFix Franchising Co, 200 S. Orange Ave., Suite 200, Orlando, FL 32801.
